

dfzfz7

in fernandezdaniel85

**+34 640782812** 

dfzfz7@gmail.com

C#

# DANIEL FERNANDEZ

## UNITY, ANDROID AND JAVA DEVELOPER

+ INNOVATION AND MANAGEMENT IN TOURISM

### **ABOUT ME**

Self-motivated Developer committed to pursuing a career change into VR & AR, aims to grow as a professional in helping people and business succeed with the digital transformation. Curious, creative and flexible team player who enjoys learning new skills. Passionate about technology and innovation, plus offering wide experience in tourism and hospitality in several countries, is ready and eager for new challenges.



Unity 3DS Max



Android Java Spring



HTML CSS



MySQL





E.Q.

- · Empathetic · Attentive ·
- · Proactive · Creative ·
- · Curious · Self-Motivated ·
- · Flexible · Team Player ·

## LANGUAGES

Spanish, Catalan (Mother tongue) English (Advanced - CAE) German, Italian (Intermediate - A2)

Russian, French - (Basic - A1)



#Travel #Gastronomy #Trekking #Cycling #eCommerce #IoT #Virtual Reality



#### EDUCATION

2020 APPLIED VIRTUAL REALITY COURSE (250H)

November 2020 - April 2021

Indústria 4.0 - Santa Perpètua de Mogoda (Spain)

Unity + 3DS Max

2020 JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER COURSE (350H)

June 2020 - November 2020

IT Academy - Cibernàrium - Barcelona Activa (Spain)

· Java + Spring + MySQL + MongoDB

2020 MASTER'S IN MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

September 2016 – January 2020

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya – UOC (Online)

• Android + Firebase + HTML + CSS + JS + Angular

2015 MASTER'S IN INNOVATION AND MANAGEMENT IN TOURISM

Septembre 2012 - February 2015

Salzburg University of Applied Sciences (Austria)

Experience Design + eTourism + Entrepreneurship

2011 BACHELOR'S IN TOURISM STUDIES

Septembre 2006 - July 2011

University of Girona (Spain)

Destination + Hospitality Management

2009 BUSINESS MANAGEMENT COURSE (ERASMUS)

September 2008 - June 2009

Plantijn Hogeschool Antwerpen (Belgium)

Business + Project Management



2011

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2020 JR. JAVA DEVELOPER @ IT ACADEMY – BCN ACTIVA (Spain)

October 2015 - November 2020

Backend Development APP and API (Project)

2020 GUEST SERVICE @ THE SERRAS HOTEL BARCELONA (Spain)

April 2015 – February 2020

Lobby, reception and concierge tasks.

2019 CHAUFFEUR/CHASSEUR @ KULM HOTEL ST. MORITZ (Switzerland)

December 2018 – April 2019 (Winter Season)

Lobby, chauffeur, porter, and concierge tasks.

2015 VOLUNTEER @ BERLIN HOSTERIA (Ecuador)

August 2014 – January 2015

 ${\bf Landscaping, gardening, animal\ care, website.}$ 

2014 F&B ATTENDANT @ NH SALZBURG CITY (Austria)

December 2012 - April 2014

F&B at bar, restaurant, room service and meetings.

2012 FRONT OFFICE @ SHERATON PRAGUE (Czech Republic)

November 2011 – September 2012

Front Office tasks, information, and problem solving.

FRONT OFFICE @ SHERATON AMSTERDAM (Netherlands)

February 2011 – July 2011

Front Office tasks, information, and problem solving.

2011 F&B ATTENDANT @ HOTEL INDALO PARK (Spain)

Summers 2002 – 2011

F&B at bar, restaurant, lounge and terrace.